saltstack.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy - SaltStack

_Updated on May 25, 2018_

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, communicate, and make use of personal information. The following outlines the SaltStack Privacy Policy:

When accessing our website, SaltStack, Inc. will learn certain information about you during your visit. Similar to other commercial websites, ours utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and web server logs to collect information about how our website is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, the time spent at our website, the websites visited just before and just after our website, and your IP address.

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document that often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the internet. Your IP address is a number used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, through the mail, and by telephone.

We are committed to keeping your email address confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists to third parties, and we will not provide your personal information to any third-party individual, government agency, or company at any time unless compelled to do so by law.

We will use your email address solely to provide timely information about SaltStack. SaltStack will maintain the information you send via email in accordance with applicable federal law.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all email sent from our organization will clearly state who the email is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all email messages will also contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further email communication from us.

**Choice/Opt Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us and our close partners at any time. If you wish to opt out of correspondence from us or our partners, click the unsubscribe link in the email or email us at [privacy@saltstack.com](mailto:privacy@saltstack.com).

**Rights to Your Data**

At any time, you may request a copy of your data or request that your data be removed from our systems by visiting the [following form](https://learn.ssaltstack.wpengine.com/unsubscribe/data-preferences) or by emailing us at [privacy@saltstack.com](mailto:privacy@saltstack.com). You may also contact us if you feel your data has been used in violation of this policy and can withdraw your consent for us to collect your data at any time. 

**How Do We Use the Information You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our legitimate business interests, providing customer service, and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

SaltStack will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

*** A Special Note About Children ***

Children are not eligible to use our website and services and we ask that minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

**How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit card information is never transmitted via email.

SaltStack may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, which information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, SaltStack uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage.

**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, personal data requests, or your dealings with our website, please contact us.

SaltStack

801.207.7440

privacy@saltstack.com
